{
  "LevelId": 16,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 154,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "CLICKABLE",
      "question": "Capable of being selected or activated with a mouse"
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "WEAPONIZE",
      "question": "To adapt something for use as a weapon"
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BASHFULLY",
      "question": "In a shy or timid manner"
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BARRELLED",
      "question": "Stored in cylindrical containers"
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BALLPOINT",
      "question": "type of pen has a small rotating ball at its tip for ink application"
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BLACKWOOD",
      "question": "type of wood is known for its dark color and is often used in furniture and crafting"
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BASELINER",
      "question": "In tennis, what term refers to a player who typically stays near the baseline during play"
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BLACKMAIL",
      "question": "Coercive threat to reveal damaging information"
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BLUEPRINT",
      "question": "Detailed plan or design for construction"
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "JACKSTRAW",
      "question": "game involves removing pieces without disturbing the arrangement"
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "JAILBREAK",
      "question": "Unauthorized escape from confinement"
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "BILLIONAIRE",
      "question": "Person with a net worth exceeding one billion dollars"
    }
  ]
}